Thank you for watching!
I was too nervous.
This way?
Where did this go?
I'm sorry. Here.
This way, yes.
Okay, let's go.
Yes, Ai, it's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
At first, I didn't care about anything else.
It's like, ooh-la-la. The theme of this song is a summer festival. Have you ever been to one? A summer festival. Yes, I have.
What did you go to? The number shot. Oh, did you get it? Yes, I did. Then we usually start with a song that gets the crowd in the groove.
This is a little after the middle of the song. It's like, "Let's sing together. Let's stop running around and sing.
Let's sing it in a tight group. I wanted to make it a song with that kind of feeling. Think of a number shot. I understand. Please sing it.
Summer Color Saiyarady, I haven't given up on this year's summer.
I've recorded many times with the Punishment Award winners.
I wrote a song called "Storm" a few years ago.
I didn't participate in the recording at that time.
I wrote a song for a commercial in Kyushu.
I also wrote a song for a commercial in Kyushu, and produced a song for a hall in Fukuoka called "Beat Goes On" that was held last year in Fukuoka.
I wrote the music for the song that was produced at a hall called "Beat Goes On" in Fukuoka last year.
I wrote a song and Nukusho and his friends came to the event.
But it was just a little bit of a project.
So this was the first time for me to finally be able to sing with Nukusho.
It was the first time I was able to sing a song with Nukusho.
It was a lot of fun.
Yes, it was nice.
Yes, it's good.
You're in a good mood.
Well, I have a couple of requests.
First of all, second line.
"I haven't given up.
Put a little Ts under "not giving up.
Little ts?
Akki.
Give up.
Then you'll end up like Green Lane.
Green Rain?
Do you know it?
Green Rain.
Oh, yes.
Green Rain is very peaceful.
There's a foreign artist called Green Rain.
Yes, I want it to be like that.
I wanted them to sing in a devilish way.
Let's make it a little worse.
Yes, sir.
Summer Sun Elevi
I'm not giving up on this whole summer
That's right, that's right
Yes.
Okay, you're starting to sound like Ranjindo.
You know Ranjindo?
I don't know.
It's difficult.
It's difficult. I'll have to learn it.
Yes, sir.
Ranjindo.
It was difficult.
Wild? It was difficult to say "wild" or "devilish" or "demonic" or something like that.
But Mr. Matsuguma taught me in a very easy way.
He taught me how to put in the little tsuo (a small part of the sound) in an easy-to-understand way, so I was able to enjoy recording the song.
Ai Kiyama has a very good sense of rhythm and a good sense of pitch, so I thought she had a very high spec.
Her singing ability as a singer is too perfect in some ways.
The way she sings, the rhythm, she gets into it so well.
At first...
But after singing it a few times, I was impressed by the interesting singing style he came up with.
Then, let's go back to the first chorus.
I'll give you a pocky if you can sing it through without me complaining.
With the product. Try it on for one shot. Number one.
Now is the only time I'll get to feel something irrevocable
I'll pick you up again today.
Good night
You win a bottle of Pocky.
Really?
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
Okay, let's put a second one on.
Yes, sir.
Payk 2.
If I can sing this well, I get a pocky today.
Is that right?
Yeah. - Okay.
What flavor?
Nothing.
Normal Pocky.
Instead, it's an extra-fine Pocky.
Extra-fine Pocky.
They're good.
They'll harden over the summer, and it'll all come together.
Want some?
Gasp!
Oh, my God.
That's not good.
They're like a bunch of incense sticks.
Okay.Okay.
Okay.
Okay, let's skip to the chorus.
Last time... when this happens... we all get closer... because we tend to go back.
Last time... that's good.
Once you get the hang of it, it's all automatic.
Yes, yes...
me
Me.
Perfect! Give me the book.
You'll be the first to win a key in Japan.
You'll be the first in history. It's usually one at a time, so you wrote that you got two in Japan.
I've always enjoyed coding, but I also like to spend time talking and communicating with the audience, even if it's not singing.
I like to spend time communicating with people outside of singing, so sometimes I wish I could spend more time recording.
I wonder how you would describe your recordings.
I wish I could sing in a cool way, and this time I sang in a cool and rocking way.
He gave me a lot of advice about how I should sing at festivals and so on.
I thought it was a lot of fun!
What do you like about Sakura-chan?
Yes.
When she sings "Sare de"...
I've always thought it was cool that she sings straight when she's stretched out.
Yes.
And I found a little habit of hers...
When you sing "yuka wa"...
I don't know if it's because I think I'm done with the last part of "wa".
You sway a little vibratically.
Only five tails.
Yes, sir.
And try to sing like you're going straight to the fifth tail there.
Yes, yes, yes.
Much better. Much better.
Personally, I think her voice is very cute.
That slightly nasal voice...
In a good way, it's an idol voice.
I think it's a good accent.
Personally, I'm the type of person who doesn't want idol voices to be the main part of the show.
But Sakura-chan's voice is cute even when she's right in the middle of the group.
But Sakura's voice is cute even when she's right in the middle of the group.
I thought it was simply a nice voice.
I can't go.
I'll try a full chorus.
Yes, please.
Great.
Thank you very much.
Um, Kiina-chan...
Yes, ma'am.
Today's theme is to sing sloppily.
Yes.
Yes, she's currently the sloppiest singer.
The way you sing now.
He's praising her.
I'm praising you.
You're the third one and the sloppiest right now.
You were in a good mood.
Thank you.
Yeah, I'm glad you liked it.
Saiyo in summer colors.
Ray Day.
Oh, my God.
Ray day.
You can't call a slut a lady.
Yes, ma'am.
All right, all right, all right.
Rayday.
Ray Day
That's right, that's right.
What kind of music do you like, Kiina?
What kind of music?
I like bands and stuff.
You like bands?
Yes, I do.
What kind of bands do you like?
You know...
Booberworld.
Ellegarden.
Aural Cyganets...
No, in a lot of ways.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Then sing like the Aural Cigarettes.
Okay.
Let's go.
Kiina, you were...
You've been the sloppiest... from the very beginning.
That's what I thought.
That's the best compliment I can give to this song.
I'd say it's the best compliment I could've given to this song, or rather, it's exactly what I imagined.
To be more specific, she can sing in a strong, Western, rock-like way.
I personally felt that it would be a new hook for Bassio as a whole.
I didn't think I would record it with that voice.
It's probably the first time I've ever done a voice like that.
It's the first time for me to sing like that.I was thinking to myself
I thought to myself, "Oh, I've discovered something new
I discovered something new.
Okay, I'm going to take a picture of you.
Yes, sir.
Uncertain future.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey!
Hey! No more cuteness of place here.
Yes, sir.
No more.
No.
Go ahead, one time.
Yes, sir.
Hey!
Woah, woah, woah, woah, woah!
Woah, woah, woah, woah!
Ugh.
Good night, Mr. *Ohkun
Looking good.
Good.
Let's put the first one in here, shall we?
I want another one.
Kina-two.
That's good.
Well, I just did a low one.
You just took a rather cross-faced shot.
And now some kind of kinky guy.
Like the singer of Rin de Shigure.
Uh...
Aww.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
No.
Stardust's biggest ever.
Make a vicious sound.
Yes, sir.
I'm not the one who's pissed.
I'm the one who's gonna be pissed.
Don't look.
Yes, sir!
Oh, no.
Okay, okay.
I don't care.
It's okay, but did I make a funny sound?
Let's try again.
Yes, I did.
I'm a little embarrassed about the making of the show.
But I want you to listen to it a lot.
Rirua!
I'm Lilua Aoi, nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you.
My name is Matsukuma.
Nice to meet you.
You've done one recording before.
This is my second time.
You're nervous.
That's not good.
Whenever I get nervous...
I try to control it.
I get even more nervous.
Let's just stay nervous.
Let's just...
I'm gonna stay nervous.
I can sing while I'm nervous.
You'll be fine.
Next time, come closer to the mic.
Yes, sir.
Rirua was very nervous at first.
Well, I'm a little nervous, but...
It's a waste of time, but I feel sorry for her, don't you?
I think it's a waste of time to film her singing when she's nervous, because it's only 50% or 60% of her real singing.
It's only 50% or 60% of a real song.
So I try to bring out 80% or more of the song, even if I can't do 100.
I'm the type of person who takes pictures with a lot of thought.
So I would use all kinds of tricks to get an erection.
I did a lot of talking.
That microphone costs about a million yen.
Don't bump it or anything.
I understand.
Would you listen to it for a million yen?
You won't listen to this.
Of course not.
It's an old microphone. They don't sell them.
Vintage.
I'd have to go back to 1967.
Time travel?
Yes, time travel.
We'll record parts of it.
But the finished product will be connected.
So even if I record only the A melody, I want you to sing until the beginning of the B melody.
On the other hand, if I say I'll record from the chorus.
But if you don't sing from the end of the B melody, the connection will be unnatural.
Yes, I understand.
This is true everywhere in recording, so please keep this in mind.
I forgot.
Here, here, I'll turn the mic over.Come on, come on, come on, Mike. I'm gonna flip you over.
When you fly.
You're the type of guy who's gonna flip the mic over.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Here comes the last take.
Can I watch one more and one more?
Sure.
Are you ready?
Canteen!
You're so cute!
Aren't you a big canteen?
It's still one small one.
Is it?
That's a real water bottle!
That's for field trips!
It's always this one.
That's the one you always use!
That's great, even when I take it to school.
That's great.
You're my lover.
You have a great voice. Quite a bit.
You look great.
Thank you. Thank you.
You have a big voice.
Really?
Yeah, in a good way.
Oh, my God.
What is it?
I've been told my voice is too quiet.
They told you?
I think you have a big voice.
Maybe it's the mic.
You have a good mic.
He said you have a good mic.
The mic.
It's like your voice is on the mic.
You know how some people say it looks good in a picture?
It's the same thing. It's called mic glide.
If you listen to it live, it sounds a little weak.
But when you hear it live, it sounds a little weak, but when it's on the mic.
It's great that there's a new way to make your voice sound like a vintage microphone.
I'm sure Alleycom will be great on the scene now.
You'd be surprised how much I've forgotten.
I heard a little bit about it in an interview earlier, so I heard a little bit about it.
You've heard the rumors?
Death Voice
I'm really excited about this song, it's coming out in late August or September.
It's like the end of August to September, like it's autumn but it's still summer and it still hurts.
I really like that season, and I like summer too.
I also like summer, but this transitional season makes me feel a little sad, which I like.
I'm not giving up on this summer, and the lyrics are a call to action.
The lyrics also have a question mark and it says, "I'm not giving up this summer.
But the second verse is something I can't forget.
So when I get to the second verse, it's like I'm almost at the end of the song.
It's a song that makes me feel like I'll never forget it.
It's a song that you can enjoy this whole summer.
I hope you will listen to this song a lot this summer.
The third line
I want you to go full throttle toward the world
Push forward, that's it.
I don't want to
I want to extend my arms.
Don't.
It's more like "don't.
Don't have it.
By the way, do you have any classmates...
Like Mr. Ide?
No, I didn't.
Have you ever met Mr. Ide?
Not often.
Not really.
No, not really.
Never.
It's like calling Mr. Ide.
Yes.
I want you to go full throttle.
Push forward.
Don't.
Whatever your dream is
Let's make it come true.
Riko-chan...
She's got a thick voice.
I knew it.
She has a natural voice.
Out of the six of us, only one has such a voice.
I'd say she has a lower middle range.
Or, to put it more simply, a diva like Hikaru Utada.
I felt that Riko has the potential to become a great vocalist.
If you watch this video
If you watch this video, please try to stretch out your lower midrange.
Many of them have a cute singing style.
Yes.
Riko is evil.
No way!
It's funny that none of them are native speakers.
Genius!
Thank you very much!
Riko-san wins 6 Pocky!
And that's the end of the first place.We're closing in first place.
Thank you very much.
Good morning.
I'm Nie Moriki. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
What kind of artists do you like?
Recently, I like Ai Myung because of my brother's influence.
Then I'll try to sing like Aimyung... at first.
It doesn't sound like Aimyung's voice.
His voice is different.
But I like her voice.
I see.
I'll take off his shoes.
I'll take them off.
Take them off.
That's polite.
I thought this is where you take off your shoes.
That's great.
Anywhere is fine.
I'll ask him to take off his mask.
OK.
I'm going to come halfway up to you.
I'll see you in a little bit.
Day one, don't be afraid. Whatever your dreams are, they'll come true.
Okay. Okay.
You have the voice of an angel.
Oh, really?
I'm sure.
Five Pocky.
Yeah, really?
You're early.
Thank you very much.
If I get five after singing "Angels," it'll be the first time in history.
Keep up the good work.
Good luck.
You're not so bold.
You seem like you've got guts.
For someone who's never recorded anything before, you seemed pretty confident.
It's something I've never seen before.
Miyu's passionate.
The national tour that's been going on for about five years has finally reached its finale.
Thank you for the encore. And now for the last song... the closing song.
Okay, please sing the closing song.
Five years is crazy!
5 years is so long!
World tour
I'm going to be an adult now
I'm definitely in the key, on the "B"!
5 years is still 20 years old today
I want to burst into twos and twos
We're breaking up after 5 more years
It's like we're breaking up with a national tour.
It'll be different, it'll be like the last tour.
I mean, it's very moving.
Thank you.
Well, I don't want you to stop.
I won't.
It felt like the last song of a breakup show.
In a good way.
I was moved.
I give it two points.
Yay! Thank you!
Seven points.
In her case...
I wonder if she had some experience in singing and lessons.
I felt for a moment that she was trying to sing well.
rather than giving detailed instructions.
I was trying to give her an image of the song rather than give her instructions.
I told him to sing it like the last song of the concert tour.
When I told him what I wanted him to do
I thought she had a lot of imagination.
I was very anxious about whether I could sing well.
I was practicing before the shoot.
But it didn't go so well.
I was so anxious.
But I received a lot of compliments.
They told me how nice it was.
I was so happy to hear that.
We really can't perform live nowadays.
Festivals are disappearing rapidly.
I think the fans are also itching to perform.
I think that's why I'm so happy to hear your message.
I think the fans are itching for a live, festival, and rock concert.
I think that's what we're trying to do now.
When we are able to perform live...
I'd like to be able to see this song for the first time at a venue or see it live online.
I want to sing along with the song so much at that time.
I want people to sing along with this song.
That's what I wanted this song to be.